片名:攻壳机动队
翻译: Fledgling Taiwan(Robert Chou)
本翻译 仅供学习交流用,请勿用于商业牟利
未来,人类与机器的界线...
IN THE FUTURE, THE LINE BETWEEN HUMAN AND MACHINE...
将会消失
IS DISAPPEARING.
先进的技术 允许用人类用生化机械来
ADVANCEMENTS IN TECHNOLOGY ALLOW HUMANS TO ENHANCE THEMSELVES...
强化他们的身体
WITH CYBERNETIC PARTS.
HANKA 机器人公司,由政府出资赞助...
HANKA ROBOTICS,FUNDED BY THE GOVERNMENT...
该公司正在发展一个 军用探员..
It is developing a military operative...
这发展 模糊了未来 人与机器的界线
That will blur the line even further.
借由移植人类的大脑 到合成物做成的身体
By transplanting a human brain into a fully synthetic body...
他们将拥有人类与机器人最强的属性特征
They will combine the strongest attributes of Human and Robot.
专案 2571
PROJECT 2571
氧气含量正在下降
Oxygen levels are dropping
大脑功能正常
brain function normal.
机器人骨架已经时负 正等待大脑转移
Robotic skeleton prepared and waiting for Brain Conversion.
启动 2571 专案计画
Initiate Project 2571.
现在 你的眼睛将要打开
Now your eyes are gonna open.
你安全了
You are safe.
没事的,只要呼吸就好
It's ok, just breathe.
只要呼吸
Just breathe.
呼吸
Breathe.
好了
Good.
很好
That's good.
你好,Mira
Hello Mira.
我是Ouelet博士
I'm Dr.. Ouelet.
你还记得任何有关攻击的事吗?
Do you remember anything about the attack?
发生了什么事?
What happened?
我...溺水了
I was...I were drowning.
到处都是水
There was water.
没错,你当时在一条难民船上
That's right. You were on a boat,a refugee boat.
该船被恐怖份子击沉了
It was sank by terrorists.
为什么我无法感觉到我的身体?
Why can't I feel my body?
Mira,你的身体损坏了.我们救不了你的身体
Mira, your body was damaged.We could not save that.
只有你的大脑还活着
Only your brain survived.
我们替你制造了一个新的身体
We made you a new body.
一个人工合成的躯壳
A synthetic shell.
但是 你的头脑,你的心灵...
But your mind, your soul...
你的灵魂
Your ghost.
仍然存在
It's still in there.
请
Please.
让她镇静一下
Sedate her.
会成功吗?
Will it work?
绝对会成功
Absolutely.
她是一个奇
She's a miracle.
机器无法指挥自己,只能遵循命令
A machine can't lead,It can only follow orders.
机器不会思考,不会关怀,没有直觉
A machine can't imagine or care or intuit.
但是 人的心灵在生化机械的躯壳里
But as a human mind in a cybernetic frame...
Mira 都可以做到,甚至更多
Mira can do all those things, and more.
她是第一个这样的生化机械人
The first of her kind.
她将加入Section 9 ,一旦她可以运作
She will join Section 9 as soon as she is operational.
请不要这么做
Please don't do that.
你简化了一个复杂的人类 成为 一个机器
You reducing a complex human to a machine.
我不认为她是一个机器
I don't think of her as a machine.
她是一个武器
She is a weapon.
也是我公司的未来
And the future of my company.
一年后
ONE YEAR LATER
第一个人工制造的记忆体加强版
The first artificially created memory enhancement.
Sirenum 训练协定是发展你能力
Sirenum training protocol is the fastest and most efficient way...
最快,最有效率的方法
to develop your ability.
比过去都强.体验一下你的力量
Stronger than ever. Experience your power.
网路犯罪是第1类犯罪.最小的惩罚:坐牢15年
Cybercrime is a Type 1 offense. Minimum punishment: 15 years in prison.
Hanka Robotics公司保证个人的安全
Hanka Robotics guarantees personal safety against.
所有巡逻区域的单位,请注意附近可能的网路犯罪活动
All patrolling area units, be advised possible cybercrime activity in vicinity.
邻近区域的空域 将被封锁住
Airspace in adjoining areas will be locked down.
Section 9 目前正在现场
Section 9 is currently on site.
我重复:所有巡逻区域的单位,请注意可能的网路犯罪...
I repeat: All patrolling area units,be advised, possible cyber crime...
这里是 上校.我在现场.
This is major. I'm on site.
等待指示
Awaiting instructions.
分析与报告
Analyze and report.
我是人类, 我有缺陷
I'm human, I am flawed.
但是 我拥抱 改变...
But I embrace change...
得以完善自身
and enhancement.
现在 我无所不能
Now there is nothing I can't do.
我无所不知,任何事我都能
Nothing I can't know, nothing I can't be.
等一下 听听这个
Wait and listen to something.
这是我4岁的女儿
It's my 4 year old daughter.
在她唱摇篮曲的同时
In the time it took her to sing that lullaby
她学会说流利的法语
she learned to speak fluent French.
你知道那首歌吗?
Do you know that song...?
有一个回音箱在那里
There is an echo box up here.
有人在扫瞄资料传送
Someone is scanning data traffic.
继续追踪它被传送到哪里
Keeps track of where it is transmitted.
看看谁值得这样的监视
To see who's worth this kind of surveillance.
进入旅馆安全网路
Accessing hotel security network.
你看见了什么,长官? 我有一大堆旅馆房间要扫描
What're you seeing,Sir? I've got a lot of hotel to scan.
有一大堆房间预留给非洲联邦的总统
There is a banquet room reserved for the President of the African Federation.
Dr. Osmond被邀请为Hanka Robotics公司的代表
Dr. Osmond is invited on behalf of Hanka Robotics.
找到了. 43楼
Got it. 43rd floor.
有人联系总统的幕僚.有人在监视他.
Someone contacted the president staff.Someone is watching him.
Dr. Osmond...
你想要从我们这 得到甚么呢?
What is it you want from us?
我想Hanka 机器人公司能提供您更多的东西
I think it is more about what Hanka Robotics can do for you.
全世界73%的人都领悟到 网路强化时代的来临
73% of this world has woken up to the age of cyber enhancement.
您真的希望被在后面吗?
Do you really wanna be left behind?
我的人民跟我一样 期待网路的强化
My people embrace cyber enhancement as do I.
没有人真正了解它的危险性..
There is no one who really understand the risk...
对个人而言,它只会与人类灵魂混再一起, 影响人的认知
To individuality, identity,messing with the human soul.
抱歉,先生们,你们走错了房间..
Gentlemen, Excuse me,I think you've the wrong...
大厅走廊,6个人,开枪射击
Hallway. Six men. Shots fired.
Section 9 ETA吗?
- Two minutes out, Major.两分钟后到达,少校
- Too long.时间太久了
我现在就去
I'm going in.
等一下
Hold!
少校,停止行动
Mayor, stop!
我过去,从你们的对手那,听过这样的讲词
I had heard this speech before from your competitors.
现在 Hanka 机器人与 Milky合作,服务很差
And now Hanka Robotics serves it with Milky suck.
这是我所说的
Look. This is what I'm talking about.
少校
Mayor!
Initiate..The hack.
启动 骇客入侵
帮我 拜托.不要杀我
Help me. Please. Don't let me die.
谁派你来的?
Who sent you?
请 帮我
Help me. Please.
回答我
Answer me!
与Hanka Robotics合作的 将被摧毁
Collaborates with Hanka Robotics will be destroyed.
你还好吗?
You okay?
你受伤了
You're injured.
你们两个 不一样
You're not the same.
嘿
Hey.
它只是一个机器人
It's just a robot!
(猫咪-记忆幻觉)
( cat,memory illusion)
(服用大脑移植,抗排斥的药物)
(take anti-rejection medicine for cerebral transplantation)
你的皮肤应该更好,身体也是.试试我们的手霜.
Your skin deserves the best, so do you.Try our hand cream.
国防部,中央办公处,第九分局
DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE,CENTRAL OFFICE, SECTION 9
在Osmond身上,有什么发现吗?
So what do we have on Osmond?
到目前为止, 几乎没有
So far, very little.
他是Hanka's 机器人部门的头头
He was the head of Hanka's robotics division.
是人类,但是有网路强化处理过
Human, but of course cyber enhanced.
他们是如何入侵他的呢?
So how did they hack him?
不知怎么办到的,那个艺妓机器人通过了他的加密
Somehow this geisha bot got past his encryption.
有点不一样
Something is different.
你有找到什么?
What'd you get?
为什么你一直认为 他没有被强化
Why you always thinking he's out there enhancing.
因为他就是
Because he is.
一个生化机器肝脏
A cyber mech liver.
已经 救我一段时间了
Been saving up for a while.
现在 每天晚上想喝多少酒 都没问题
Now it's lost cool every night.
你强化它 为了可以 多喝点酒吗?
You got enhanced so you can drink more?
拥抱强化,Togusa.没有它我们就不会在这里
Embrace enhancements, Togusa.We would not be here without it.
(Togusa) 我是快乐的全人类.谢谢
I am all human and happy, thanks.
有从艺妓机器人 找到更多资料吗?
Any more information about the seized geisha bot?
Hanka正在扫描
Hanka is running scans.
Dr. Dahlin将时负帽ǜ,但是...
Dr. Dahlin will have the reports ready but...
我已经跟首相说了
I've been talking to the Prime Minister.
他要全部完整的报告
He wants a full report.
Togusa.
在昨晚的攻击事件之后
Following last night's attack...
又有3个Hanka的科学家遇害
3 more Hanka's scientists were murdered...
就在公司的中央实验室里
in the company's central laboratory.
前两个是被枪杀
The first two were shot...
第3个是被他自已的机器人活活打死
and the third was beaten to death by his own service robot.
他们的大脑 都被骇客入侵过
All showed signs of cerebral hacking.
与艺妓机器人骇入Osmond 一样
The same as the geisha did to Osmond.
而且他们 都是在Hanka 的资深人士
And all were senior figures... in Hanka.
如同Osmond一样
Just like Osmond.
在每个犯罪现场都留下一份留言
A message was left at each of the crime scene...
留言的人自称是
By someone identifying himself...
Kuze
as Kuze.
与Hanka Robotics合作 就得被消灭
Collaborate with Hanka Robotics should be destroyed.
与Hanka Robotics合作
Collaborate with Hanka Robotics...
就得被消灭
should be destroyed.
Togusa.
你跟Ladriya去向Hanka总裁 Mr. Cutter 说
You and Ladriya go speak to Mr. Cutter,the CEO of Hanka.
Major 和 Batou 去看看 Dahlin 的报告
Major and Batou take a look at Dahlin report.
从修复的艺妓机器人 身上找出点东西
Find out what has been recovered from the geisha.
少校
Major!
我告诉过你不要 跳下去
I told you not jump off.
我必须如此做,不然 会有更多人死亡
I had to, or more would have died.
你是我小队的一员,是我的职责
You are a member of my team,and my responsibility
我会找到他 把他杀了
I'll find him... and I will kill him.
这就是制造我的目的,不是吗?
It's what I am built for, isn't it?
你不只是武器
You are more than just a weapon.
你有灵魂,魂魄
You have a soul, a ghost.
当我们看到 我们的独特性 是一种美德
When we see our uniqueness as a virtue...
只有这样 我们才能找到心灵的平静
Only then will we find peace.
安全地 重新配置孩子的遗传结构
Safely reconfiguring the child's genetic Structure.
家庭才会更好
Families built better.
昨晚在旅馆生气地离开,你是怎么了?
What was going on with you at the hotel last night?
没事,我很好
Nothing. I'm fine.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
嘿,亲爱的,要升级吗?
走开
- Hey, sweetheart, want an upgrade?
- Move.
我有任何你想要的东西
退下
- I have anything you want.
- Back off!
嘿.Ming
Hey, Ming!
嘿,Batou
Hey, Batou!
来拿你要的骨头
谢谢
- Got your bones.
- Thanks man.
给狗吃的
For the dogs.
对不喜欢人群的你来说,你怎么会这么喜欢狗呢
For someone who doesn't like people How come you care about dogs so much
我不知道.我喜欢流浪狗 而他们喜欢我
I dont know. I like just strays and they like me.
他们喜欢你是因为 你j养他们
They like you Because you feed them.
你真没良心
You got no heart.
嘿,女孩们
Hey, girls!
嘿,Gabriel
Hey Gabriel!
见见 少校
Meet Major.
少校,这是Gabriel
Major, Gabriel.
我以前有养过狗
we used to have a dog.
真的吗?
Sure of it?.
我还以为你喜欢猫呢
..more of a cat person.
你从来不谈论这些事
You don't talk about that stuff.
什么事?
What?
你的过去
我不记得太多 我的过去
- Your past.
- I don't remember much.
只有一些片段,碎片的记忆
Just fragments, bits and pieces.
你的家人呢?
What about family?
我的父母,带我们来这个国家时,死了
My parents, they died bringing us to this country.
我们的船沉在港口
Our boat sank in the harbor.
我几乎被淹死
I almost drowned.
我总觉得..
I feel sinking...
有浓浓的雾 遮住我的记忆
there is always this thick fog over my memory.
而且 我怎么都看不透
And I can't seen through it.
你很幸运
You are lucky.
我每一天 都被我的记忆所困扰著
Every single day I get screwed upon my memory.
最好是清澈 单纯的
It's better to be pure.
跟你一样(没有记忆)
Like you.
(记忆 幻觉)
(memory illusion)
Hanka机器人公司,中央办公室
HANKA CENTRAL OFFICE OF ROBOTICS
欢迎来到Hanka Robotics
Welcome to Hanka Robotics.
所有的参访者必须 随时出示 应有的证件
All visitors must display appropriate credentials at all times.
请 张开 合紧手,
Opens and close, please.
你的内部系统受损了
Your have damaged internal systems.
也许 下次,你可以帮我设计 好一点
Maybe next time you can design me better.
你好吗?
我很好.我无法感觉到任何东西.
- How are you?
- I am fine. I can't feel anything.
No you, in There.
不是指你.我是指 精神上.
经常出现幻觉
I have been having glitches...
但是 都会消失
but it will pass.
你有服用药物吗?
有的
- Have you been taking your medication?
- Yeah.
但是这些幻觉常出现.今天早上出现过两次.
But these wounds are so cycling.I had two this morning.
是声音 还是 影像?
两者都有
- Sound or image?
- Both.
我找到了
I see it.
你有做任何未加密的下载吗?
You made any unencrypted downloads?
没有,请帮我删除他们
同意吗?
- No. Just delete them from me.
- Consent?
我的名子是少校Mary Killian
我同意删除这些数据
My name is Major Mary Killian.
I give my consent to delete this data.
完成了
It's done.
没什么大不了的.
他们是什么?
- No big deal.
- What are they?
是你记忆里的感官回波,阴影
Sensory echoes from your mind, shadows.
我不确定
I'm not sure.
你怎么知道那是我的幻觉呢?
How do you know it's a glitch of what's me?
这些幻觉有不同的结构
The glitches have a different texture...
相对于你的其他编码
to the rest of your code.
我可以看到任何东西
I can see everything.
所有你的想法,你的...决定
All of your thoughts, your... decisions.
人类才有隐私
I guess privacy is just for humans.
你就是人类
You are human.
人们视你为人类
People see you as human.
我周围的每个人 似乎都适应的很好
Everyone around me seems to fit.
他们似乎与 某东西相连.而我
They seem connected to something.Something I...
没有
am not..
好像 我没有过去
当然,你有过去
- Like I have no past.
- Of course you have a past.
到时候,你会感觉到越来越多 与过去的相连
And at time you'll feel more more connected to it and to them.
请 张开 合紧手
Opens and close, please.
我们执著於记忆 好像 记忆定义了我们是怎样的人,但是
We cling to memories as if they define us, but...
并非如此
They really don't.
我们的所做所为 才定义我们是怎样的人
What we do is what defines us.
你正在进入Hanka 安全区域.只有受权的人 可以进入.
You're entering a Hanka secure area.Authorized personal only.
请关闭 沟通增强功能
Please disable communication enhancement.
我很忙
I'm busy.
Dr.. Dahlin,你弄完了吗?
Dr.. Dahlin! Are you finished yet?
如果你没有 用大量子弹 射击艺妓机器人
If you hadn't rained all the Geisha with the bullets,
这会简单一点
This would be much easier.
我没有射他
是我射的
- I didn't shoot him.
- I did.
这工作要花好几天
This is gonna take days.
我必须执行 好几百个可能的模拟
I need to run hundreds of potential simulations.
我们没有时间了
We don't have the time.
她以前是Hanka公司的机器人
She was a Hanka companion bot.
但是 她的大脑被骇入,程式被窜改
But she was reprogrammed for cerebral hacking.
她的硬碟里有什么?
What was on her drives?
没有东西.资料都被摧毁 当它被运来的时候
Nothing. The data was destroyed as it was transmitted.
没有迹象显示 她是来做什么的
No sign of what she was up to.
硬体被毁坏了
The hardware was vandalized.
他们把它破坏得很彻底
They ripped her up.
我必须做个深潜 进入它的大脑,来找出线索
Then I have to do a deep dive.
做深潜 你将无法 加密保护自己
You can't encrypt you in the deep dive
我知道
I know it.
他们可以在她身上留下陷阱.大量的脉冲波,病毒
They could left traps in her.Mag pulses, viruses.
她是对的
She is right.
你会暴露你的心智给骇入她的人.你将会门户大开.
You will be exposing your mind to who ever hacked her. You'll be wide open.
我必须进入她的记忆中.这是最快找到Kuze的方法
I have to get inside her memory.It's the fastest way to find Kuze.
那太危险了
It's too dangerous.
而且一点也不可靠
And highly irresponsible.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
如果你看见任何 病毒码朝向我来.就把我拉出来
You see any bad code headed my way,pull me out.
你怎么一直在出汗,比我还紧张??
How come you're the one sweating?
执行它
Run it.
网路心智连线到少校,现在启动
Cyber mind connection to the Major,now active...
而且 不加密
and unencrypted
请同意必须的资料下载
consent required for data download.
我的名子是少校Mira Killian,我同意
My name is Major Mira Killian and I give my consent.
断开连线,把她拉出来
Disconnect. Get her out.
把她拉出来
我在试,但是她 被骇客入侵了
- Get her out!
- I'm trying, but she's being hacked.
把她拉出来 ,现在
Get her out now!
现在
Now!
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
我知道Kuze 他在哪里了
I know where he is.
两个佣兵在门口.持有武器 而且是加强型的
Two mercs at the door.Armed and enhanced.
收到,我们来搞定它
Copy that. We got it covered.
夜店里好热闹
There's a lot of heat in here for a nightclub.
它是Yakuza黑帮的夜店.热闹是很正常的.
It's a Yakuza club. What did you expect?
我蛮喜欢这样的地方
I quite like the place.
你喜欢,我一点都不惊讶?
Why doesn't that surprise me?
我必须引起一些注意.
看看我能否进入地下室
I am gonna have to draw some attention.
See if I can access the basement that way.
你不是来找麻烦的吧?是吗?
You're not here looking for any trouble, are you?
我是来找姑娘 和 喝啤酒的
I am just here for the girls... and beer.
我能为服务的吗?
我在找人的
- Can I help you?
- I am looking for someone.
不曾来过这里吗?
You've been here before?
我的朋友 在这里做机械工
My friend had some mech work done here.
我们这里 不做机械工的
We don't do mech work here.
打扰了,是我搞错了
My mistake.
为什么不来与我们欢乐一下?
我们有隐密的地方
Why don't you come have fun with us?
We will have some privacy.
我进来了
I'm in.
我会在这里 当需要我的时候
I'll be here when you need me.
说的朋友在这里工作?
我说我的朋友 曾经 在这里工作过.
- You say your friend worked here?
- I said my friend had work done here.
她是人类吗?
She's human?
的朋友.
Your friend.
这话是什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
Batou.
你能听到我吗?
Can you hear me?
谁替你做了这个 惊G的工程
Who did this stunning work on you?
非常完美 与众不同
It is divine.
Ladriya 枪
Ladriya... guns.
这里
Here.
Batou,我失去讯号了
Batou, I'm losing signal.
e担心.甜心
Don't worry sweety.
这里很隐私,没人会打扰
We have privacy.
听着
Listen.
讯号进不来 也出不去
You know the signal is green in or out.
少校,我已经就位.你收到吗?
Major, I'm in position. Do you copy?
啤酒
Beer.
如果不回答,会伤了我的心
If you don't answer,you're gonna hurt my feelings.
Ladriya,能收到少校的通讯吗?
Ladriya, do you have major on Comms?
什么都没有.讯号被屏蔽住了
Got nothing. The signal is still blocked.
我想我已经感到无聊了
I am afraid I get bored by that easily, so...
不想说
You don't wanna talk...
也许你想跳支舞
Maybe you wanna dance!
少校.快点.回答我
Major, come on. Answer me.
我以为你说没有麻烦
I thought you said no trouble.
跳舞
Dance!
事实上...
The truth is...
我不是被制造来跳舞的
I wasn't built to dance.
通讯恢复
我正在前往后面的房间
Back on comms.
I am heading to the back room.
好的.我会在哪里与你碰头
I missed you. I'll meet you there.
与Hanka Robotics合作,就得被消灭
Collaborate with Hanka Robotics should be destroyed.
少校?
Major?
Batou 在哪里?
Where is Batou?
在强化中,隔壁房间. 他没事
In enhancement, next door.He is doing well
你承受了 大部分的爆炸
you took most of the blast.
我看见他(Kuze)在那里
I saw him down there.
好像
It was like...
他(Kuze)正等着要见我
He waited to see me.
我们的神经突触 扫描了你
We synaptic scanned you.
所有你目睹的 都送到第9区分部 去评估
Everything you witnessed went to Section 9 to evaluate.
你知道,扫描中..
You know, the scan...
你出现许多的幻觉
Also turned up the number of glitches.
幻觉变得 越来越严重了
They've been getting worse.
从什么时候开始的?
Since when?
从做了深潜后,开始的
Since the deep dive.
任何一个幻觉 对你有特e的意义吗?
Do any of the glitches mean something to you?
没有
No.
他们没有
They don't.
你进入 那个人用过的 躯壳里
You have been inside the same shell as he has.
那会产生非常严重的后果
That could have very serious consequences.
你未经授权 深潜进入 技艺机器人
You were not authorized to deep dive the geisha.
我对你很失望吗?
You're disappointed.
不,我是担心你
No, I'm worried.
你并非无懈可击
You're not invulnerable.
我可以修复你的身体,但是 我保护不了你的心智
I can repair your body,but I can't protect your mind.
为什么不能?
Why not?
你可以看到我的思想
You can see all my thoughts so...
所以你应该可以保护它
You should be able to secure them.
试着了解 你有多重要,Mira
Try and understand your importance Mira.
有一天,每个人都会变得跟你一样
You're what everyone will become one day.
不了解 我现在是多么地孤单
You don't know how alone that makes me feel.
我能看到在门外,知道吗
I can see you out there, you know.
我手里有几根手指?
How many fingers am I holding up?
好笑(中指)
Funny.
说点好听的
Say something nice.
这是你自己选择的吗?
You chose those?
战术上的需要
They are tactical.
你总是为了工作
我还有e的选择吗?
- Always for the job.
- What else I got?
这眼睛很适合你
是吗?
- They suit you.
- Yeah?
我有夜视的能力...
I have night vision,...
还有 X 光透视的能力
and X-rays.
我猜 我能看到 你所看到的东西了
I guess I see like you now.
e担心,你会习惯它的
Don't worry, you'll get used to it.
谢谢你救了我
Thanks for saving my ass.
很高兴 看到你没事
Glad to see you're okay..
少校
Major?
你能帮我j狗吗?
Could you feed the dogs for me?
我不想吓到它们
I don't want to scare them.
没问题
Anytime.
你的资金不够吗?Mr. Aramaki
Are you insufficiently funded, Mr. Aramaki?
第9部门缺少了关键性的运作资源吗?
Is section 9 missing some critical operational resource?
我们有 我们所需的一切, 不缺东西
We have everything that we require.
少校是我们最尖端的武器,只要她完好无缺
Major is our most sophisticated weapon only if she is intact.
而且Dr. Ouelet告诉我...
And Dr. Ouelet informed me...
你让她 深潜到一个 损坏的艺妓机器人
That you let her dive a corrupted geisha.
你应该知道Hanka公司,对政府而言
You realize there is a premium importance
是多么的重要
that Hanka represents to this government
少校是我公司的未来
Major is the is the future of my company.
如果 你再一次让她受损...
If you compromise your systems again...
我会把你这部门 烧了
I will burn this section.
是的,先生
Yes sir.
Mr. Cutter.
小心 谁才是 我们的威胁
Be careful who is the threat.
我对首相负责,不是对Hanka公司 负责
I am accountable to the Prime Minister,not to Hanka.
创造你自己的美丽
来美丽强化
Create your own beauty.
Beauty enhanced.
是人类吗?
Are you human?
是的
Yeah.
能把它脱掉吗?
Can you take that off?
好让我看看你的脸.
So I can see your face?
这是什么感觉?
What is that feeling?
感觉
It feels...
很不一样
different.
是什么?
What are you?
安全专案计画 2571
SECURE PROJECT 2571
Hanka 个人档案
HANKA PERSONNEL FILES
看着我
Look at me.
告诉我,他们从我这里,拿走了什么
Tell me what they took from me.
我很抱歉.他们从没有告诉过我
I am sorry. They never told us.
用这双眼开车,感觉怪怪的
It feels weird driving with these eyes.
为什么要服药物?
Why do you take that?
好让我的头脑,不会排斥这个身体
Um, keeps my brain from rejecting this body.
少校,Batou,你们必须到这里来
Major, Batou, you need to get here.
什么情况?
What you got?
又一个Hanka科学家被杀了
Another Hanka scientist has been found dead.
是Dahlin 博士
It's Dahlin.
收到
Got it.
少校 这里走
Major this way.
安全 专案计画2571
SECURE - PROJECT 2571
那是什么?
What is that?
她找到了 Kuze 从 Osmond 偷走的东西
She found what Kuze stole from Osmond.
是替专案计画2571的工作人员名单
It's a list of everyone who worked on a project called 2571.
这就是Kuze的目标
That's who he's targeting.
名单上还有其他人吗?
Is there anyone else on that list?
Dr. OUELET
现在,快去找到 Oulet.
Find Oulet. Now!
她正在路上.她的通讯不通
She is in transit. Her comms are down.
我正看着她,心理想着...
I'm looking at her and thinking...
要我付赡养费, 还要我付小提琴的钱
"You want me to for pay for violin too".
你不要误会
Don't get me wrong.
我很爱我女儿的
I love that chick to pieces.
真的.她很令人惊讶
I do. She is amazing.
可是 听她拉小提琴,真是痛苦呀
But when she prox that thing,it's painful right?
为什么不学钢琴呢?
Why not piano?
我意思是 学费都是一样的嘛.听起来也不错
I mean, it's the same price,and doesn't sound so bad.
至少 如果你弹的不怎么样,它听起来...
At least if you can't play that proper,it sounds...
2571! 告诉我所有一切你知道的
2-5-7-1!Tell me everything!
你时负靡为2571 而死吗?
Are you prepare to die for 2-5-7...?
走
Go!
谁是Kuze?
Who is Kuze?
为什么 他要杀Ouelet?
我什么 都不知道
- Why does he want to kill Ouelet?
- I don't know anything.
够了 ,够了
Enough, enough!
我们需要他活着
We need him alive.
求求你,我已经说过了
Please. I have been trough this.
你们抓错人了
You have the wrong guy.
那么,告诉我们 你是谁
So tell us who we do have.
我的名子是Lee Cunningham
My name is Lee Cunningham.
你从哪弄来的武器?
我不知道
- Where'd you get the weapons?
- I don’t know.
谁把枪放在车上的?
Who loaded the mines?
我已经告诉过你, 我不知道武器的事
I don't know anything about the weapons,alright I told you.
我正要去接我的女儿
她要去上小提琴课
I was picking up my daughter.
She takes violin lessons.
你女儿的名子是什么?
What's her name?
这是她吗?
是的
- Is this her?
- Yeah.
她像是个小天使,是吗?
Isn't she a little angel?
这是你女儿?
对
- This is your daughter?
- Right.
有孩子吗?
Do you have that?
你住在哪里?
Where do you live?
我不记得了
I can't remember.
好像是很高的地方
是座高楼
I think it's a tall place.
Is it a tall building?
是很高的地方,对吧?
It's a tall place, right?
你根本没有孩子
You don't have a child.
你没有老婆.你一个人独居.那才是你.
You have no wife. You live alone,It's just you.
什么? 不
我们去过你的公寓
- What? No.
- We went to your apartment.
那里没有人
不
- There was nobody there.
- No.
你一个人在那里住了10年
You live there for 10 years by yourself.
不
No.
你在说谎
我没有说谎
- You're just lying.
- I'm not lying.
我没有杀任何人
I didn't kill anyone!
为什么你要这样对我?
Holocube 中断连线
- Why do you keep doing this to me?
- Holocube disconnect.
拜托
Please!
我没做任何事
I didn't do anything.
为什么 你一直这么对我说?
Why do you keep saying this to me?
我不了解.他怎么 都不知道?
I don't understand. How can he not know?
骇客入侵他的头脑,造成一段记忆真空
Kuze 抹除了他的记忆
The hack must have created a vacuum.
Kuze's wiped his memory...
而且 不知怎么地 植入了一个新的现实
and somehow installed a new reality.
至少 他相信他有一个孩子
At least he got to believe he had a kid.
那有什么不同呢?
What's the difference huh?
幻觉,真实?
Fantasy, reality?
作梦,记忆?
Dreams, memories?
全都一样
It's all the same.
都是噪声,毫无意义
Just noise.
是他
It's him.
他来了
He is in there.
这隔间是安全有屏蔽的.他不可能进得来.少校
This cube is secure. He can't be, Major.
测谎仪
Lie Detector.
他一定是从那入侵的
He must have hacked in that way.
我们必须上传到机器.追踪编码.锁定他的位置
We should uplink to the machine,trace the code, get a lock on his location.
快去做
Do it.
不要进去那里
太危险了
Don't go in there.
It's too dangerous.
少校
Major
我们不知道他还能做什么
We don't know what else he can do.
讯号不是很稳定
我们能锁定他吗?
The signal is unstable.
Can you get the lock on him?
我们必须快点.我们快要失去他了
We gotta move fast. We're losing him.
连线中
Connecting.
你是谁?
Who are you?
到这里来
Come here.
我很害羞
I'm shy.
我不像你...
I'm not beautiful...
那么漂亮
like you.
告诉我你是谁
Tell me who you are.
我出生过很多次了
I have been born more than once.
所以我有很多的名子
So I have more than one name
我会找到你
I'll find you.
我会等着
Not yet.
事情还没结束呢
I am not done.
机器正在追踪他的位置
The machine is tracing his location.
找到他了
We got a fix!
我必须看到我女儿
I need to see her.
不,拜托.我知道..
No Please. I know..what...
我们找到他了
We got him.
我们走吧
Let's go.
武器上膛
Weapons up.
出发
- Go.
- On me.
趴下  趴下
Stay Down! Stay Down!
放下 放下
Put it down, put it down.
手榴弹
Grenade!
少校
Major!
请回话
Come in.
我知道为什么,我们无法找到他了
I knew why we could not find him.
他利用人类的心智,来制造一个属于他自己的网路
He is using human minds to create a network of his own.
我们马上过去你那儿
We're coming to your position.
告诉我你是谁
Tell me who you are.
我就是你在找 你要摧毁的人
I'm that what you seek to destroy.
在此生,我的名子是
In this life, my name is...
Kuze.
你正在对我做什么?
What are you doing to me?
我把你,连线到我自创的网路上
I have, connected you,to a network of my own creation.
当我在这个世界死去后..
When I am finished in this world...
我的灵魂可以在那里 生存,然后再生
my ghost can survive there and regenerate.
你想对我怎么样??
What do you want from me?
我对你
I became...
很著迷
Fascinated with you...
当你在那艺妓机器人里面时
Reading your code...
我读取你的编码
when you were inside that geisha.
我从来没有感觉到 是如此的
Like nothing I had felt before,yet so..
亲近 熟悉
Familiar.
我们是一样的
We are the same.
我们不一样
We are not the same.
你杀害无辜的人
You kill innocent people.
无辜?你认为他们无辜吗?
Innocent? Is that the..what you call them?
我被他们 制造成这样
I am as they need me.
是谁制造你的?
Who made you?
他们是怎样告诉你的?
What have they told you?
说你是第一个
That you were the first?
第一个大脑抢救成功的人
The first cerebral salvage.
你是我失败教训后 出生的
You were born of lessons that I was failed...
你在胡说些甚么?
What are you talking about?
我还神智清醒时,他们支解我的躯体时,然后G弃了我
I was conscious while they dismembered my body, and discarded me
如同垃圾一样
like garbage.
我躺在手术台上
I was lying on a table...
听着医生说 我的心智无法匹配
Listening to doctors talk about how my mind had not matched with the shell.
他们造的躯壳
That they had built.
我就是专案计画2571的产物
I'm projected to 2571...
而且是 失败的产物
had failed...
然而 他们继续执行计画
and they had to move on...
在你身上
to you.
你真漂亮
Morning beauty you are.
他们把你改进了许多
They have improved you so much...
在制造我以后
since they made me.
他们认为我们会是 他们人类未来进化的一部分
They thought that we would be a part of their evolution.
但是 他们制造我们 好让他们能进化
But they have created us to evolve alone...
...
超越他们自己
beyond them.
那就是你所说的进化吗?
Evolution? That's what you call?
杀掉每个制造你的人
Killing everyone who made you?
你根本没有 听进我所说的话
You are not listening to me.
你是杀人凶手
You are murderer.
是他们先要杀掉我的
They tried to kill me first.
我是出于自卫
It is self-defense.
保护我自己
The defense of myself.
还会死更多人
More will die...
直到他们告诉我
until they tell me...
他们从我身上拿走了什么
what they took.
我绝不允许你继续杀人
I won't let that happen.
你要杀了我吗?
You want to kill me?
如同其他人一样
Like everyone else.
那就杀吧
Do it, then.
做你的程式要你做的
Do what you are programmed to do.
那是什么?
What is that?
我不记得了,但是它经常缠绕着我
I kick in to remember,but I am haunted by it.
你看过它吗?
Do You see it?
Togusa!
不要服用他们给你的药物
Don't take the medication that they gave you..
他们用药物抑制你的记忆
They use it to suppress your memories.
你的躯躯壳属于他们的,但是 你的灵魂不是
Your shell belongs to them,but not your ghost.
你的灵魂是你自己的
Your ghost is yours.
记住我的话
Remember that...
也许 你能想起 过去的一切
and maybe you can remember it all.
离她远一点
给我趴在地上
Get away from her!
Get down on the ground now.
少校
Major..
Major!
很多
Dozens.
有多少
How many?
在你之前,有98个实验 没有成功
98 unsuccessful attempts before you.
你杀了98个无辜的人
You killed 98 innocent people.
不,我没有杀过任何人
No, I didn't kill anyone.
如果不是 那些实验
if it weren't for those experiments.
你不会存在,你也不会在这里
You would not exist .You wouldn't be here
实验?
Experiments?
我是你的实验品
不
- Is that what I am to you?
- No!
不,Mira
No, Mira!
牺牲是必须的
Sacrifices were made.
那些躯体是从哪来的?
Where did the bodies come from?
我是从哪来的?
Where did I come from?
Mr. Cutter 把他们 带来给我们的
Mr. Cutter brought them to us.
我没有多问他
I did not ask questions.
港口
The harbor.
我的父母
My parents.
他们的死因
The way they died.
是真的吗?
Did that happen?
不
No.
是我们给你 植入的假记忆
We gave you false memories.
Cutter想以此 激励你
Cutter wanted to motivate you.
用以 打击恐怖份子
我没有同意
To fight terrorists.
I didn't approve.
这很残忍,但我的工作 很重要
It was cruel, but my work,that was important, and...
所以你诞生了
you were born.
你是如此漂亮 完美
You were so beautiful.
我拥有的 都是假的
Nothing I have is real.
我找到他了
I found him.
我告诉过你 要小心
I told you to be careful.
你一直 都知道他是谁
You knew who he was the whole time.
是你制造他的
You built him.
他有一个
He had a..
不稳定的暴力心智
Violent unstable mind.
他的大脑连接 不受约束
His cerebral connection wouldn't hold!
我试过救他
不
- I tried to save him!
- No.
你留下他等死
You left him to die.
还没找到Kuze,先生
待会儿,检查上层区域
Nothing on Kuze yet, sir.
Checking upper zones next.
有少校的消息吗?
Is there any word on Major?
她悄悄地走了,离开了 "网格"
She's gone.Off-grid. Silent.
收到,先生
Copy that, sir.
我知道哪里可以找到她
I know where to find her.
注解:"网格" 是用大批个人电脑,相互网路链接,分散运算
达到 超级电脑 的运算速度
我没叫你过来这里
I didn't ask you to come here.
你从来不叫我
You never ask.
可是我每次都来
But I always do.
是他们派你来 带我回去吗?
Did they send you to bring me in?
我是来这里钓鱼的,你看到鱼吗?
I'm just here to fish. Did you see any?
你是公司的人马,你要遵守规定.
如果他们要你杀掉我呢?
You are a company man, you follow orders.
So, if they ordered you to kill me.
e说那些屁话. 会惹我生气的.
Stop saying shit like that.You're gonna piss me off.
水下面怎么样?
What's it like down there?
又冷 又黑
It's Cold and dark.
好像另一个世界
Just a million miles away.
没有声音
No voices.
没有网路数据流
No data streaming.
什么东西
Just...
都没有
nothing.
很吓人
那,你为什么要下水
- It scares me.
- Then Why do you do it?
有真实感
It feels real.
为什么你不阻止Kuze?
Why didn't you stop him?
我不知道 还有谁 可以相信
I don't know who to trust anymore.
你信任我,对吗?
You trust me, right?
是的,我信得过 你
Yes I do.
只是 不喜欢 像你一样
I just don't like it.
我需要你带我回去
I need you to take me back.
还有很多事要查
There is more I need to find out.
好吧
Sure.
Dr. Ouelet...
你告诉了她什么?
What have you told her?
她知道
She knows.
我要抓她 回来
I'm bringing her in.
Hanka 保安 向总部报告
Hanka security to Headquarters.
我们抓到 少校了
We have the Major.
为什么给她 打镇静剂?
Why is she sedated?
她被恐怖份子 策反了
She's been turned by a terrorist.
但 你已经知道
But you know that already.
她去找你时,你就应该 通知我了
You should have called the first time she came to see you.
然而, 你却告诉她一切讯息
Instead, you gave her information.
凭什么让你认为 你有...
What makes you think you have the..
权力告诉我这些?
2571计画 让我们关门了
- Right to tell me that?
- 2-5-7-1 took us close.
该是走向 下一个阶段的时刻
It's time to move on to the next iteration.
2571计画没有失败
2-5-7-1 is not a failure.
我可以 删除她所有的资料,重新给她输入程式
I will delete all the data and reprogram her.
她将 完全不记得他(Kuze)
不 不 不 不
- She won't remember him at all.
- No, no, no, no.
你把所有恐怖份子的数据,都下载下来
You download all the data on the terrorist...
然后 我会命令你 终止执行计画
and then I order you to terminate.
什么?
我们要制造一个更好的
- What?
- We'll build one that's better.
我会删除所有的东西
你以前也删除过
- I'll delete everything.
- You deleted before.
她(少校)是我的
不
- She's mine.
- No.
她(少校)是你我合约的一部分
She is a contract... with me.
我们成功了
We succeeded.
她比人类强,也比 人工智慧机器人 强
She is more than human... and more than AI.
我们改变了她整个身体
但她的灵魂还在
We change her entire identity.
But her ghost survived!
她的灵魂 就是 让我们失败的原因
Her ghost is what failed us.
我们无法控制她.她已经没有价值了
We can not control her. She is no longer a viable asset.
应该由你 处理掉 她
You should be the one to do it.
你要对我做甚么?
What are you doing to me?
我要执行标实 脑部突触神经 扫瞄
I'll run the standard synaptic.
上传你的数据资料
Upload your data on the raid.
我会嗜返 知道 Kuze告诉了你些什么
I'll find out exactly what Kuze told you.
你知道 他告诉了我什么
You know what he told me.
真相
The truth.
你要删除 我所有的数据资料,对吗?
You're deleting everything, aren't you?
不
No.
这样,我就会忘记..
So I don't remember...
你
You.
我的名子是少校Mira Killian..
My name is Major Mira Killian...
我不同意 删除这些数据资料
And I do not consent to the deletion of this data.
我不同意
I do not consent.
我们不再需要你的同意
We never needed your consent.
不需要你的同意 或 任何人的同意
Yours or anyone’s.
你要杀了我
You're killing me..
是吗?
Right you..?
Mira?
你听到我吗?
Do you hear me?
Mira?
这是你的过去,真正你的过去,拿好
This is your past, your real past. Take it.
守卫
快走,快走
- Guards!
- Come on, come on!
快点! 走呀
Come on, go!
走呀!
Go!
安全警报 第25层楼
Security alert on level 25.
启动 封锁程序
Initiating Lockdown procedure.
请前往 指定的安全室
Please relocate to your designated safe room.
谢谢您的合作
Thank you for your cooperation.
那就是 人心的造成的问题
That's the problem with the human heart.
我要看她的扫瞄
I want to see her scan.
她杀了Ouelet博士
She killed Dr. Ouelet.
你不能再跟她联络了
Hanka保安部门 将会追捕她
You are to have no further contact with her.
Hanka security will hunt her from here.
你下了什么命令?
格杀无论
- What are the orders?
- To terminate on sight.
你要杀了她吗? 是你创造她的
You want to kill her? You built her!
叫你的中士退下.
少校 绝不会杀Oulete博士的
- Have your sergeant stand down.
- The Major would never hurt Dr. Oulete.
她现在已经不再是少校了
She is not the major anymore!
我们的第9区探员 被恐怖份子 安置程式
We have a section 9 operative under terrorist programming.
如果这件事 公诸於世,你的单位就完了
This goes public your unit goes down.
你杀了她..
You kill her...
就等于 杀了我们
You kill us.
我会考虑 你的意见
I'll take that under advice.
怎么办?
So what now?
喔,小猫咪.
Oh, the puppy.
喔. 吓了我一跳
Oh, you surprised me.
它喜欢
She likes you.
我在找..
I was looking for...
不,进来吧
No, come in.
好的,来,来,进来吧
Yeah, go, come come.
喝点茶好吗?
好的
- Can I offer you some tea?
- Okay.
P s a g m e n o . com
那是 Motoko(素子)的房间
That... Motoko's room.
我的女儿一年前死了
My daughter died a year ago.
我很遗憾
I am Sorry.
她离家出走了
She run away.
她不好管教
She was a difficult.
而且 她跟我常吵架
We fought.
但是 我想 我们全都是这样成长过来的,不是吗?
But I guess we all fight with our parents, right?
请过来坐呀
Please come on the sit.
她怎么死的?
What happened to your her?
我不知道
I don't know.
政府部门把她的骨灰送来给我..
The ministry sent me her ashes, and...
他们告诉我 她自杀的
They told me she took her own life.
但是 Motoko(素子) 不会这样
But Motoko... No, no, no.
我不相信他们
I never believe them.
她过得很快乐..
She was happy...
跟一堆她的朋友 住在不法之地
living in the lawless zone with her friends.
她发表过声明
She'd write her manifestos about...
说 科技会
how technology was...
毁灭这个世界
destroying the world.
然后 有一天
Then one day...
警察来了
the police came...
然后 他们就逃了
and they run.
太奇怪了
It's strange.
我在很多年轻女孩身上 看到了她的身影
I see her in so many young women.
在大街上,在我梦中
On the street, in my dreams.
仿佛 她还活着
As if she is still here.
她
She was...
很勇敢 无所畏惧
fearless.
而且 很野
And wild.
让我想到了她
You remind me of her.
抱歉
Sorry.
为什么我会让想到她呢 ?
Why do I remind you of her?
是看我的方式
The way you look at me.
是谁?
Who are you?
我也不知道
I don't know.
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait!
会再来看我吗?
Will you come again to visit me?
我会的
I will.
Aramaki.
听我说
Listen to me.
根本就没有恐怖份子 袭击难民船
I was never in a terrorist bombing.
我的父母..
My parents...
都是他们装在我记忆中的数据
Everything was data they installed in my mind.
而且还有其他 像我一样翘家的人.
And there were others.Run-aways like me...
都被他们抓走,拿去做 用完即G的实验
considered disposable.
Kuze过去也是这样.这是 为什么 他要回来
Kuze was one of them.That's why he's coming.
向Hanka公司 复仇
To Hanka.
能证明 所说的吗?
Can you prove this?
Ouelet博士可以证明
Dr. Ouelet can.
Ouelet博士死了
Ouelet's dead.
Cutter说是杀了她
Cutter says you killed her.
把我放在网格上.我需要Kuze来找我
Put me on the grid. I need Kuze to find me.
我们会向 Cutter 表明这事
We will be exposed to Cutter.
我知道,但是我必须这么做
I know, but I have to do this.
我要去与首相开会
I'm going to meet with the Prime Minister.
Cutter 必须被阻止
He must be stopped.
病毒已经扩散了
The virus has spread.
所有的干员 盯紧心灵通讯
All agents stick to mental comms.
不要送一只兔子
Don't send a rabbit...
去杀一只狐狸
to kill a fox.
我们著火了(被盯上了)
We are burned.
重复
I repeat.
我们著火了(被盯上了)
We are burned.
我们再网格上找到少校了.她在不法之地.
We have located Major on the grid.She's in the lawless zone.
空中支援 5分钟后出发
Air support 5 minutes out.
蜘蛛坦克 在行动区域吗?
Is the spider tank within range?
是的,先生. 正等待您的命令
Yes sir. Awaiting your orders sir.
Motoko(素子)!
这是真的
It is real.
这个地方
This place.
我记得当时 他们对我们做了什么
I remember what they did to us.
Cutter 和他的人马.在这里,他们把我们抓走
Cutter and his men.This is where they took us from.
我们 过去睡在这里
We used to sleep right here.
我们像家人一样
We were like a family.
我们都是 翘家的人
All of us run away.
我们什么都没有
We had nothing...
除了彼此的关怀
except each other.
可是,彼此关怀 也被他们夺走了
They took that from us.
你过去的名子是 Hideo(秀雄)
Your name was Hideo.
Motoko(素子).
那是的名子
That was your name.
Motoko(素子).
跟我来
Come with me...
进入我的网路王国
my network.
我们会进化 超过他们的
We will evolve beyond them.
我们可以一起为
他们过去 的所做所为 进行报复
And together we can avenge
what they have done to us.
来吧
Come...
跟我一起
with me.
我可以从这里 遥控
I will take control from here.
手动操作 武器系统
Weapons system manual command.
蜘蛛坦克启动
Spider tank now active
是Cutter. 他发现我们了
It's Cutter! He found us!
锁定目标
Target acquired
不
No!
目标被消灭
Target eliminated.
你 差一点就赢了
You came close...
你这个怪胎
you freak.
马达控制中心受到入侵
Motor center compromised.
有狙击手在现场吗?
Sniper team on site?
正在接近目标中,先生
Approaching the target now sir.
跟我来
Come with me.
这里不能待了
There is no place for us here.
不
No.
我不想离开这里
I'm not ready to leave.
我属于这里
I belong here.
我会永远与你同在
I'll always be there with you...
与你的灵魂同在
your ghost.
发现目标
Target is in view.
那你们还在等什么?
What are you waiting for?
开枪呀
Do it!
不
No!
继续射击
Keep firing.
Saito,你找到少校了吗? 她安全吗?
Saito, have you found Major? Is she safe?
她会的
She will be.
嘿
Hey..
Hey.
说点好听的
Say something nice.
的名子是什么?
What's your name?
Aramaki 告诉我 过去有一个名子
Aramaki told me you had a name from before.
Motoko(素子).
少校还在里面,对吧?
Major still in there, right?
是的
I am.
Mr. Cutter.
我跟首相谈过了
I talked with the Prime Minister.
你被指控谋杀与叛国罪
You are accused of murder and crimes against the state.
我就知道 会是你
I thought that it might be you.
你反抗是不智的
It is unwise to resist.
求你 e杀我
Please.
少校
Major?
我正与Cutter 在一起
I am with Cutter.
在我杀他之前,有什么话要对他说吗?
Do you wanna say anything before I kill him?
告诉他 这是正义
Tell him this is justice.
这就是我 被创造的目的
It's what I was built for.
所以 愿意给予同意了
So do you give consent?
我的名子是少校
My name is Major.
我同意杀了他
And I give my consent.
不必 再来墓园这里了
You don't have to come here anymore.
我知道
I know.
我的心智是人类的
My mind is human.
我的身体是机械的
My body is manufactured.
我是第一个这类的人,但是..
I am the first of my kind, but...
我不会是最后一个
I won't be the last.
我们执著於记忆 来定义我们
We cling to memories as if they define us.
但是 定义我们的 是我们的行为
But what we do defines us.
我的灵魂活着 为了提醒未来的我们
My ghost survived to remind the next of us...
人性 才是我们的美德(价值)
that humanity is our virtue.
我知道我是谁
I know who I am...
也知道 我活着 是要做什么
and what I'm here to do.
少校
Major.
与目标交火
Engage targets.
已被授权
You're authorized.
谢谢欣赏
翻译: Robert Chou